Paulina Skurska-Kaczmarek

p.skurska.kaczmarek@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/paulinaskaczmarek (210) 993-9582 Austin, TX

SKILLS

Research

Surveys Interviews Data & task analysis Insight Synthesis Proto - personas A&B Testing Usability Testing Journey Mapping Empathy Mapping

Design

UI graphics Storytelling User flows Concept sketches Style guides

Prototyping & Wireframing

Storyboarding
Decision mapping
Rapid prototyping & testing
Interactive flow
Usability testing

Tools

Sketch Adobe Illustrator Adobe Photoshop Adobe XD Invision Html/Css- basics

Collaboration

Analytical thinking Ability to work under pressure Great attention to detail Strong work ethic and team player Eager to learn new things Open - minded analytical thinker with international background. Currently, finishing an in-depth UX design certification with UT Austin. Following my passions in bridging art and problem-solving. Seeking an entry role as a UX Designer in a company where I can collaborate with local and international team members to create beautiful, useful software solutions.

PROJECTS

Amazon user flows redesign - https://tinyurl.com/ybu9fkx6

Redesign of Amazon website and application based on thorough research. Introduced minimal interface design and efficient site search functionality

Food Vibe - restaurant's application - https://tinyurl.com/y72a9a7e
Designed from scratch application which helps users find best place to eat.
Introduced moodboards idea to allow users visualize perfect restaurant

HUD.gov website and user flows redesign - https://tinyurl.com/yb28bzw9
Redesign of HUD.gov website based on thorough research and A/B testing.
Created new style guide, logo and introduced streamlined user flows

Wall Street Journal web and app redesign- https://tinyurl.com/ybw66tat
Redesign of WSJ web and app incorporating Atomic Design.
Created visually pleasing layout based on grid system and prominent CTAs

EDUCATION

The University of Texas at Austin, Texas — The Ux/UI Design Bootcamp
June 2018 - Dec 2018

Gdansk University of Technology, Poland — *Master of Science*Sep 2013 - Jun 2015 Field: **Management** Specialization: **Operations Management**

Gdansk University of Technology, Poland — Bachelor of Science
Sep 2009 - Jun 2013 Field: Engineering Management Specialization: Production
systems engineering

EXPERIENCE

Freelance, San Antonio, Texas Austin, Texas Oct 2015 - Present

graphic design (logos, branding, design briefs, style guides), creating content for websites, redesigning existing websites and applications, user research, usability testing

Soltec Services, Gdansk, Poland - Payroll and Human Resources

Payroll and Human Resources Specialist Apr 2012 - Sep 2015 Human Resources Administrative Assistant Nov 2009 - Mar 2012

participating on board meetings in regards to payroll policy, spearheading initiative to simplify payroll processes, responding to employee inquiries regarding payroll issues;